[
  {
    "question": " Simple synchro system is used for ",
    "choice1": "To turn light load ",
    "choice2": "to turn heavy load  along with other components",
    "choice3": "both",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What to check in PCB :",
    "choice1": "Extra Copper foil should be removed ",
    "choice2": "Base material should be free from flaking",
    "choice3": "both",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How to identify  anode and cathode  photo diode",
    "choice1": "A tab extending from  cathode ",
    "choice2": "Anode is larger than cathode ",
    "choice3": "Color coding ",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": " Cmos used in ",
    "choice1": "manual system",
    "choice2": "aircraft system ",
    "choice3": "track system ",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": " IC is mounted on",
    "choice1": "Surface of processor ",
    "choice2": "Core of processor ",
    "choice3": "",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 2
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "Damper is used in servo system for ",
    "choice1": "Oscillation in high speed ",
    "choice2": "spinng in high speed ",
    "choice3": "Both",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Power supply in a torque synchro ",
    "choice1": "rotor stator both in parrlel ",
    "choice2": "",
    "choice3": "",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "TTL VOLTAGE ",
    "choice1": "3",
    "choice2": "4",
    "choice3": "5",
    "choice4": "6",
    "answer": 3
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "which one is heavily doped",
    "choice1": "base",
    "choice2": "collector",
    "choice3": "emmiter",
    "choice4": "",
    "answer": 3
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": " COLLECTOR IS ALWAYS REVERSE BISED W.R.T ",
    "choice1": "EMMITER ",
    "choice2": "BASE  ",
    "choice3": "COLLECTOR ",
    "choice4": "alert('Hello World');",
    "answer": 2
  }
  
]
